[{"answer": "No, no, we haven't the time. Talk prose. Where is my play", "docId": "Shakespeare-in-Love.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "God be praised!  Locked", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "What does my friend care of that? He is readying the Curtain for my friend", "docId": "Shakespeare-in-Love.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I have, Master Shakespeare", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Do you think", "docId": "Shakespeare-in-Love.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": " The daughter of his enemy", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "I thought your play was for my friend", "docId": "Shakespeare-in-Love.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": " A different one you haven't written", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Who are you, master", "docId": "Shakespeare-in-Love.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": " I'll be damned if you are", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "A moment, sir", "docId": "Shakespeare-in-Love.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": " I am the money", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Two hours at prayer", "docId": "Shakespeare-in-Love.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Piety is for Sunday! And two hours at prayer is not piety, it is sel", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Piety is for Sunday! And two hours at prayer is not piety, it is sel", "docId": "Shakespeare-in-Love.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "It would be better that you tell her to get off her knees and show some civility to her si", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Answer me only thi", "docId": "Shakespeare-in-Love.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Then kiss me again for I am not mistook", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "\"Madam, your mother craves a word with you", "docId": "Shakespeare-in-Love.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "\"Marry bachelor, Her mother is the lady of the hous", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": " Not ready? Where is she", "docId": "Shakespeare-in-Love.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " Will you ask Her Majesty to be patient?", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": " To be the wife of a poor player", "docId": "Shakespeare-in-Love.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Then I will go with you", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Speak out! I know who I am. Do you love stories of kings and queens? Feats of arms? Or is it courtly love", "docId": "Shakespeare-in-Love.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": " They are not acted for you, they are acted for me", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "My Massacre at that place is complete", "docId": "Shakespeare-in-Love.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "You have the money", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "I am going to church", "docId": "Shakespeare-in-Love.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "It is to be expected on a Sunday", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "You were not dead before. When I thought you dead, I did not care about all the plays that will never come, only that I would never see your face. I saw our end, and it will come", "docId": "Shakespeare-in-Love.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "If not that place the Queen will know the cause and there will be no more my friend", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "It's true, Wil", "docId": "Shakespeare-in-Love.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Not the billing, the bill", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "A hired player no longer. Fifty pounds, my friend, for the poet of true love", "docId": "Shakespeare-in-Love.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "It was we ourselves did that. And for my life to come I would not have it otherwise", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "I am done with theatre. The playhouse is for dreamers. Look where the dream has brought us", "docId": "Shakespeare-in-Love.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "I have hurt you and I am sorry for it", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "It was we ourselves did that. And for my life to come I would not have it otherwise", "docId": "Shakespeare-in-Love.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "If my hurt is to be that you will write no more, then I shall be the sorrier", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "But all ends well", "docId": "Shakespeare-in-Love.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "I don't know. It's a myster", "qsentId": 42}]